justbats.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy | JustBats.com

## Personal Information

We are 100% PCI compliant and our pages utilize HTTPS for all data transmission.

We may collect and store any identifiable information that you choose to provide in connection with your use of the JustBats.com Sites. This may include personally identifiable information (such as your name, shipping address, billing address, email address, phone number and credit card number) that we need to process your orders, communicate with you, or provide you with services that you request. For example, through order forms on the JustBats.com Sites, we collect personally identifiable information necessary for shipping products that you purchase. We also may collect your financial information (like your credit card number and billing address) and your contact information (like your email address, phone number, and shipping address). We use state-of-the-art encryption software with every order called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology; this software scrambles your information, so it is virtually impossible for anyone but JustBats.com to read. Once your information reaches us, our security system is intended to keep your data stored safely as it is important to us that you feel confident about using and making purchases through the JustBats.com Sites.

_Customer Feedback:_ Some areas of JustBats.com, like the Testimonials page, allow users to write comments. We also encourage our customers to provide feedback about the JustBats.com Sites by contacting us at [support@justbats.com](mailto:support@justbats.com). We use all of this information for the sole purpose of improving the experience for all JustBats.com customers, whether it be providing user feedback about our products before purchasing, following up with customers who claimed to have an unsatisfactory experience, or taking the advice to improve the functionality of the website. We store emails, testimonials, product reviews, and product questions and answers within our database for these purposes. By submitting these Submissions directly through our website, you give us your consent to review and publish them on our pages for others to see. In submitting testimonials, users may choose their name and location, which allows them to essentially submit testimonials and feedback anonymously.

## Use of Personal Information

Financial information that we collect is used to bill you for products that you request. Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about JustBats.com to you. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the "How to remove your name from our mailing, sharing, or email list " below.

If you register for email or if you provide your email address to us, we will send you emails. These emails will inform you of our launch of new products, of special sales, of promotional offers from our partners, and other information related to your use of the JustBats.com Sites.

We use your shipping address to ship your products to you. We use your billing address, if different than your shipping address, to verify your billing information. We never share our customer names or addresses, email addresses or other personally identifiable information, other than to the extent described in the "Disclosures of Your Information " section below.

## Disclosures of Your Information

JustBats.com will not disclose personal information about you to other companies, persons or agencies, except for the purposes described below:

_Service Providers:_ We employ other companies and individuals to perform certain services and functions on our behalf. Examples include operating and maintaining our Site, taking orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing consultation and assistance, distributing customer surveys, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These companies have access to personal information needed to perform their services or functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

_Compliance with the law and Terms of Use_ \- We may release personally identifiable information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request. Also, to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of JustBats.com, our customers, our employees or others.

_Business Transfers:_ As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, customer information is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing privacy policy (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, if Beapro Sports, LLC, JustBats.com or substantially all of the assets including the JustBats.com Sites are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.

_Sharing:_ We may share your name and email address with other reputable companies so they may send you information about products of potential interest. But, we will not share credit card information. If you prefer that we not share your name and email address with other companies, please see "How to remove your name from our mailing, sharing, or email list " section below.

_With Consent_ \- Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have the opportunity to choose not to share information.

## How to Remove Your Name from the JustBats.com Mailing, Sharing, or Email List

You also may use the following options for removing your information from our database so as not to receive future communications, or to no longer receive our service, or to not share your name and address with other companies.

1\. You may send an email to [support@JustBats.com](mailto:support@justbats.com).

2\. You may send mail to the following address: Customer Service, JustBats.com, 10800 North Pomona Ave., Kansas City, Missouri 64153.

3\. You may call the following telephone number: [1-866-321-BATS (2287)](tel:1-866-321-2287).

4\. In commercial emails that we send you, you may use the "opt-out" or "unsubscribe" option included in the email itself.

## How to Correct Your Information the JustBats.com Mailing, Sharing or Email List

You have the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:

1\. You may send an email to [support@JustBats.com](mailto:support@justbats.com).

2\. You may send mail to the following address: Customer Service, JustBats.com, 10800 North Pomona Ave., Kansas City, Missouri 64153.

3\. You may call the following telephone number: [1-866-321-BATS (2287)](tel:1-866-321-2287).

## Non-Personal Information

_Session Analytics Information._ We may automatically collect non-personally identifiable information about your hardware devices (i.e., your computer or mobile device) when you access the JustBats.com Sites. For example, when you visit JustBats.com, we may collect your Internet Protocol ( "IP ") address, which is the number automatically assigned to your computer or mobile device whenever you access the Internet, as well as information about the type of Web browser software you use and the referring Web site. This number does not identify your name, email address, or other personal information. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our service and to administer the Site. We may also collect information about your activity on our Sites, such as the time and duration of your visit, the sections of the Site that you visit, the search terms you use, and the products you add to your shopping cart.

_Cookies._ A Cookie is a bit of text code that we develop and store on your computer's hard drive. It helps us to identify your computer when you visit us again. After you register with our website for the first time, we assign a Cookie to your computer's hard drive so that upon returning to our website, we identify you as a registered user. Cookies do not collect personally identifiable information.

The Cookie is uniquely yours, and will only be read by the website that issued the Cookie. Cookies are used to collect information from your computer. Some Cookies we may use are temporary, meaning that they expire once you close your browser. Some Cookies we may issue remain on your computer's hard drive so that when you return to our website, we can identify your computer as a previous user and customize your unique web experience.

By using cookies we will be able to see how our website is used. This means that we will be able to identify the most popular areas of the website and make it easier for you to access them. They also help us to be more efficient as we can learn what information is important to you.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can disable this function by changing your browser settings if you so wish. You can delete the Cookies from your computer's hard drive if you wish. If you delete our Cookie from your computer's hard drive, however, and then visit our website again, you will be treated as a first-time visitor since we will not be able to identify your computer. If you would like to remove cookies, you can do so by following Internet browser help file directions. You may decline to accept cookies by modifying your Web browser settings. If you choose to decline cookies, however, you may not be able to sign up for or use certain features of the JustBats.com website that depend on your Web browser accepting cookies.

JustBats.com, its advertisers, and ad servers may also use cookies, as well as files called "Web beacons" or "clear gifs" to determine on an anonymous basis which advertisements and promotions our users have seen and how users responded to them. However, we do not use these technologies to collect personally identifiable information.

## User Age

We do not sell merchandise for purchase by children via the JustBats.com Sites. If you are under 18, you may use the JustBats.com Sites only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. Should a child whom we know to be under 13 send personal information to us, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child to inform him or her that we must have parental consent before receiving his or her personal information.

## External Links

The Privacy Policy outlined herein pertains only to the JustBats.com Sites and does not pertain to any other companies whose pages you can navigate to from our the JustBats.com Sites, such as our many bat manufacturer partners. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policies and practices of any third parties. PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT ADDRESS THE PRIVACY OR INFORMATION PRACTICES OF ANY THIRD PARTIES.

## Changes and Notification

If we ever make alterations to this privacy policy, we will do our best to inform our customers of the changes. We will notify those who have signed up with us for email offers via email, and we will post a noticeable message on our home page once the changes have been implemented. Customers reserve the right to disagree with the privacy policy in any form and discontinue business with JustBats.com.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, contact us by email: [support@justbats.com](mailto:support@justbats.com), Live Chat, or our toll-free phone number: [1-866-321-BATS (2287)](tel:1-866-321-2287) and we will make our best efforts to respond within 24 hours.

Effective Date: January 18, 2013
